wearpact.com 2016-06-08

# Privacy Policy | Wear PACT

###### Our Commitment To Privacy

At PACT, we value our customers and respect your privacy. This policy describes the personal information we collect about you, why we collect it, and how we use it. If this policy changes, we will post an updated version on our website. You will know if the policy has changed by checking the revision date that appears below. If you have any questions about our privacy policy, please navigate to wearpact.com/contact-us and submit a ticket at any time. Customer service will get back to you within 48 hours. 

Privacy Policy Last updated November 3, 2015 

###### What Kind of Information Does Wear PACT LLC Collect?

We may collect personal information from you, such as your name, email address, postal address, phone number, and credit card number when you place an order online or by phone, create an account with us online, contact us with a question or concern, or participate in a contest, promotion, or survey. We only store your order history and contact information. We do not store your credit card information on our servers. 

When you visit wearPACT.com, we collect navigational information, such as browser type and version, service-provider identification, IP address, and the site from which you came. Navigational information is largely anonymous in the sense that it doesn't contain your name, address, phone number, email address or other information that directly identifies you. 

PACT and its marketing partners use form elements and/or cookies to collect information and enable certain technology solutions used to operate our online store and to market our products. A cookie is a short line of text that attached to your browser when you visit a website or view a particular advertisement. This cookie can then be identified to determine how often you have visited a site or seen particular ad. Cookies are otherwise generic, and cannot be used to access any other information on your computer. 

PACT uses cookie data we collect to operate, maintain, enhance, and provide all of the features, information and services outlined at **wearpact.com**. PACT may also use this information to understand and analyze the usage trends and preferences of our users, to improve the way the site and PACT technology works and looks, and to create new features and functionality. Cookie data may also be used by PACT marketing partners to enhance our customers' advertising experience on wearPACT.com or other venues across the internet. 

###### How Does Wear PACT LLC use my Information?

We may use your personal information in the following ways: 

  * To process and fulfill your order, including to send you emails to confirm your order status and shipment
  * To communicate with you and to send you information by email, postal mail, telephone, or other means about our products, services, contests, and promotions, unless you have directed us not to contact you with promotional communications
  * To administer and fulfill our contests and other promotions
  * To analyze trends and statistics
  * To contact you if necessary

We may use your navigational information to analyze trends and traffic to our website. 

###### Does Wear PACT LLC Share my Information?

When you place an order on wearPACT.com or by phone, your credit card information is securely transferred to Cybersource, one of the largest and most trusted payment gateway providers. Your contact information is sent to our warehouse so that they can fulfill your order. 

PACT does not share your information with any other third party other than those outlined above unless we are required to do so by law. 

###### How do I Access or Change my Information?

You can review and change certain personal information related to your use of wearPACT.com (such as your name and contact information). To access your information, simply log in to your account using your email address and password, and you will be able to edit your personal information in your customer dashboard. 

###### How Do I Make Choices About Receiving Promotional Communications?

PACT wants to communicate with you only if you want to hear from us. If you prefer not to receive promotional information, such as information about special offers and sales events, you can let us know by contacting us via wearpact.com/support. Additionally, you can opt out of email messages at any time by clicking the “opt-out” link at the bottom of any marketing message you have received from us. 

Please be sure to include your full name and the email address you used when you registered with or made a purchase on wearPACT.com or by phone. If you ask us to remove your name and address from promotional lists, we will maintain your name in a "do not contact" file to ensure that we can honor your request. It may take up to 10 days to process your email request, during which period you may continue to receive communications from us. 

Please note that when you make additional purchases at wearPACT.com or by phone, we will continue to confirm your order status and shipment by email. We may also need to contact you via telephone, email or postal mail with questions or information regarding your order. 

###### How do I Know my Personal Information is Secure?

We do our best to provide you with a safe and convenient shopping experience. When you enter your personal information on wearPACT.com, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us and then to Cybersource for payment processing. If you have accessed our secure server, the first characters of the address in the URL should change from "http" to "https". 

###### How do I Know my Personal Information is Secure?

We do our best to provide you with a safe and convenient shopping experience. When you enter your personal information on wearPACT.com, we use Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect your information as it is transmitted to us and then to Cybersource for payment processing. If you have accessed our secure server, the first characters of the address in the URL should change from "http" to "https". 

###### What is Phishing and How do I Avoid It?

"Phishing" is a scam designed to steal your personal information. If you receive an email that looks like it is from us asking you for your personal information, do NOT respond. We will never request your password, username, credit card information or other personal information through email. 

###### What About Links to Other Websites?

For your convenience and information, our website contains links to other sites, which may have privacy policies that differ from our own. We are not responsible for the content or practices of any linked site. We recommend that you review the privacy policy of any site that you access through our sites.
